Ariana Baseman

arianamb@yahoo.com | 248-635-8470

linkedin.com/in/ariana-baseman | github.com/Abaseman0514 | Portfolio: https://bit.ly/2Htubgn

I pay close attention to detail and work to find quick, yet accurate, solutions to technical problems. With previous experience as a property management professional and one of the first Lyft drivers in Metro Detroit I excelled with roles in customer service, sales, leasing, training, communicating with C-level executives and processing financials. Through all of my work, I have taken a solutions-focused approach to solving problems for others and seek to apply that same approach with clean and clear communication and processing.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Specialist

January 2020 - Present

TTEC, Work@home

- Bank of America Consumer, Senior Client Associate: Promoted May of 2021 to help Agents find answers in knowledge base and assist with more challenging clients
- Bank of America Consumer, Agent: Hired as a permanent employee to assist Consumer Deposits with claims/disputes, account maintenance, etc.
- Bank of America Small Business CoVid project: helped customers file disputes/claims, replace debit cards, etc
- With American Red Cross Project, assisted in routing calls to the proper department (3 months)

Web Developer December 2018 - Present

Freelance

• Working on various projects, most notably, Oak City Grille in Royal Oak, keeping their website up-to-date and adding a calendar of performances. Taught myself SquareSpace as their site had already been created using that platform.

Driver/Midwest Driver Advisory Council Representative

April 2014 - Present/May 2015 - January 2017

Lyft, Metro Detroit

- Served as one of seven drivers across the nation appointed to the first Driver Advisory Council
- Created content and articles for the Lyft blog and community websites
- Helped interview, on-board and train new drivers, as well as assist applicants through the hiring process
- Manages Detroit market Facebook group and coordinates special projects with head office and local teams

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- SquareSpace / WordPress
- Data Structures & Algorithms
- Microsoft Excel, Outlook, Word, Powerpoint
- Google Sheets, Docs
- Slack/Skype

EDUCATION

Grand Circus, Detroit, MI

December 2018

After Hours Front-End Development Bootcamp

Projects include: AHBC_Midterm_WAM: https://bit.ly/2J1qb5v Movie Lab: https://bit.ly/2ABz4A7
Final project: WeatherWhere https://bit.ly/2CaziiH (GitHub)

American University, Washington DC Bachelor of Arts, Public Communication Minor: Political Science May 1999

ADDITIONAL ROLES

Collage.com, Customer Service Specialist, at home, seasonal Property Management: Leasing, Accounting, A/R, A/P, Collections The Urban Institute, Washington, DC - Communications Associate

Sept-Dec 2019 2006-2016

2001-2003

Summers 1992-1996

Public Interest Research Groups (PIRG), Michigan and Washington, DC - Canvasser/Field Manager